Yauhen Varapayeu - Frontend Developer (React)

Telephone number: +375447008632 E-mail: amidawolf@gmail.com

LinkedIn profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/evgeniy-voropaev-aw/

RSSchool profile: https://app.rs.school/cv/47d6664e-aad2-4312-80ec-760719fd196b

github - https://github.com/AmidaWolf

English: A2+ (https://www.efset.org/cert/Ra48Ur)

Summary of Qualifications

Start programming in 2019 after studying at RS School (JavaScript, React). Worked as a freelance web developer within a team of backend developer, designer and team leader. In 2022, I upgraded my skills at RS School (Typescript + React + Redux). Total experience 1.5 years. In high priority, looking for a full-time remote work.

Technical Skills

Programming languages and technologies: React, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS/SCSS

Programming practices: Agile, Kanban, Code review

Tools: GIT, Webpack, VS Code, Webstorm, Figma, Photoshop

Professional Experience

Freelance, 08.2019 - now

Irrelevant Experience

Architecture and Construction LLC, director, 05.2013 – now

Projects

PMA - project management app

Project: https://pma-team38.netlify.app/

Source: https://github.com/Tianika/project-management-app/tree/develop

Position: lead developer

Environment: react, redux, axios, i18next

RSLang - web app for learning English

Project: https://rslang-amidawolf.netlify.app/ **Source:** https://github.com/AmidaWolf/rslang

Position: team lead, developer

Environment: JS, TypeScript, SCSS, webpack

ProjectInterClassic - architectural company site

Project: https://piklassik.com/

Source: https://github.com/Tianika/project-management-app/tree/develop

Position: developer

Environment: react, redux, axios, i18next

Hobby and fun weekend projects

Portfolio site

Project: https://awportfolio-site.netlify.app/

Source: https://github.com/AmidaWolf/react-portfolio

Position: developer

Environment: react with hooks, styled components

JJIT with local deploy

Source: https://github.com/ArchiKeV/jjit

Position: developer **Environment:** JS, CSS

Education

RSSchool JavaScript/Front-end (https://app.rs.school/certificate/tn7crqcd) - 09.2021 - 03.2022\$

RSSchool React (https://app.rs.school/certificate/bupdbh09) - 03.2022 - 06.2022;

English: A2+ (https://www.efset.org/cert/Ra48Ur).